YI-CHENG KUO (Jerry)

Senior Software Engineer / Android Developer

Scarborough, Ontario

🙀 E-Mail: <u>narikuo@gmail.com</u>

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/yi-cheng-kuo/

SUMMARY

More than ten years of experience in the IT industry, including more than three years of experience in designing, developing, testing, and maintaining mobile applications in the education and IoT industry, and five years of experience for Web applications for Business Process Management and website. 2+ years of experience in computer and operating system maintenance.

Familiar with Android, Kotlin, Java, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, and CSS. In addition, there are rich experiences in developing and maintaining WordPress.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Supervisor

Wistron Corporation / New Taipei City, Taiwan

August 2021 ~ Feb 2022

- Project: Rehabilitation program record App (Keeogo) for Android devices in the medical and healthcare industry
- Involved in the project's full development life cycle, including requirements gathering, design, implementation, and deployment.
- Developing new features for the application using java and android SDK.
- Java, Kotin, RESTful API, Retrofit, MQTT, OpenVidu, MPAndroidChart, Scrum.

Advanced Software Engineer

Wistron Information Technology & Services Corp. (Wistron ITS) / New Taipei City, Taiwan November 2018 ~ July 2021

- Involved in the project's full development life cycle, including requirements gathering, design, implementation, and deployment.
- Developing new features for the application using java and android SDK.
- Responsible for the maintenance of the Smart Classroom project (Remote Controller, e-Bulletin Board, e-Schoolbag, Multi-media Teaching Box).
- Responsible for developing new features for WiParents APP for Teacher-Parent communication (Android and iOS).
- Worked on updating and distributing the app via Google Play.
- Project development and technical support.

Senior Field Application Engineer

Alltek Technology Corporation / Taipei City, Taiwan

November 2015 ~ October 2018

Involved in developing and maintaining Android mobile application project about

Bluetooth E-lock, USB Smart Meter, Smart Plug with Alexa Skill.

- Evaluation, planning, design and development of application project.
- Responsible for UI/UX planning and design for the APP.
- Project development and technical support, research on solutions and industry trends.
- Building and maintenance of the website for the IoT platform project.

Senior Software Engineer

Alltek Technology Corporation / Taipei City, Taiwan

December 2009 ~ November 2015

- Responsible for the website development, design, maintenance and management.
- Responsible for E-Form of the Business Process Management system and Enterprise Information Portal (EIP) development and maintenance.
- Project development and technical support.
- Website architecture, traffic control, network security planning and troubleshooting.
- Network systems and database maintenance and technical support.

Information Technology Specialist

Fu Chen Paper Corporation / Taipei City, Taiwan

September 2002 ~ April 2009

- Responsible for the company's website development, design, maintenance and management.
- Responsible for maintaining and managing the sales system, computer software, and hardware equipment.
- Sales and marketing support.



Y AWARD

Outstanding Employee Award 2011

Alltek Technology Corporation

Valuable Services Award 2019

Wistron ITS



EDUCATION

Chung Yuan Christian University / Taoyuan, Taiwan

Bachelor of Science, Civil Engineering

1996-2000

SKILLS

- Java, PHP, JavaScript, ¡Query, HTML, CSS, XML, JSON, GIT, MySQL, MS-SQL
- Android Studio, Visual Studio Code
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator
- WordPress (Content Management System)
- Photography